cx.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy

We want you to know how we treat personal information we may obtain from you as a website visitor. By using our website, you accept both this Policy and our Agreement.

Policy – This Online Privacy Policy applies to this website and to services offered through it, unless and to the extent that the written privacy policy for a service states otherwise.

Sharing Policy – It is our overall policy not to disclose to others outside of us and our affiliates, vendors and business partners any personally identifiable information about our customers without their prior consent. We do not sell or provide your personal information to parties unconnected with the services we provide without your permission.

### Information We Collect

Website Visitors – When you access our website, we automatically collect access log information about your visit, including information such as the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses assigned (numbers assigned to your computer while online), bandwidth used, system and connection performance, browsers used, dates and times of access, and Internet resource requests, including requests to access web pages. Online Registrants – In visiting our website, if you register with us or participate in a contest, survey or online transaction, we may ask for certain PII. When we ask you for such information, we will tell you how it will be used and you may elect not to participate.

Cookies – We, or a vendor that places advertising on our websites, may use “cookies” to collect information about your visit to our website and to manage information concerning your preferences. A “cookie” is a small computer code added to a file on your computer as a record of its visit. It does not collect or provide your name or any other personal information about you. It can, however, be used to note information about your visit, such as your type of web browser, operating system and Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, to better tailor the site for you. It can also be used to recognize you when you log in as a registered user or as a repeat visitor returning to our website. This allows us to tailor our site by remembering you and any options you select. We may share non-personal information obtained from the varying kinds of cookies with vendors, advertisers and others. You can control what cookies are accepted by your computer through the settings on your web browser or by deleting them from your files. Doing so, however, may limit the personalization available to you.

Third-Party Cookies and Web Beacons – These forms of computer code are sometimes placed by advertisers or others with connection to a webpage and may be read by the advertisements provider. They may use a form of code called a “web beacon” or “clear GIF.” These are usually contained in a transparent image on a page or in an image on an email message and serve as a way to gather information about your visit, such as your Internet Protocol Address and information or statistics about your visit. As with cookies, you can use your browser or app settings to control web beacons.

Behavioral or Interest Based Ad Options – We and other website owners or advertisers may use cookies or similar tools to provide customized ads based on visits to their websites. You can find more information about these tools, including benefits they can provide at http://www.networkadvertising.org. Many companies that collect information for behavioral advertising are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). NAI offers the ability for you to opt-out of the behavioral advertising programs of their members by going to http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp or http://www.aboutads.info/choices. Please note that if you use a different computer, change your web browser, or delete your cookies, you will need to renew all of your opt-out choices.

Advertisers and Other Websites – We do not control the privacy policies of advertisers or of websites you may link to from our websites or by using our services. You should review their websites for questions about their Internet security and privacy.

### Use and Sharing

Use Policy – We consider any personally identifiable information we receive about you to be confidential, and it is our policy to use it only in providing our websites and services – from sales and installation, to operations, administration, advertising, marketing, support, network provision, maintenance, communications with you, billing, collection and similar ways. We may also use such information in dealing with fraud and unauthorized use of our services. We may associate personal account information with data from third parties about you or similar persons to better predict your product and service preferences for use in programming, advertising transactions and to market our services to you.

Aggregate Information – We use aggregate information about our customers and website visitors for a variety of purposes. Such aggregate information does not identify individual customers. We may share such aggregate and related demographic information with third parties.

Retention Policy – We may retain personal customer information in its regular business records as long as someone is a customer or until no longer needed for business or legal purposes.

Special Exceptions – We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information in our possession if we have a good faith belief that it is necessary to: (1) comply with the law or legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property or those of others; (3) respond to fraud, abuse or unauthorized use of our services; (4) enforce our Website Visitorsí Agreement and Terms of Use, our Acceptable Use Policy or related standards; or (5) act in an emergency to protect your safety or that of another. We may also share information if we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business operations, merge or combine with another organization.

Third Parties – We sometimes use affiliates, vendors or third party partners in association with this website and may provide personally identifiable information about users for such purposes. In providing such information, we require that the outside party maintain at least the same level of confidentiality that we maintain for such information. In addition, any use by the vendor or third party may not exceed that needed to provide its service.

Internet Communications – Unless addressed to us, we do not read email messages, instant messages, online chats, or the content of other online communications. We may however, retain and provide such communications if we are legally required to do so. Incoming and outgoing email messages are generally scanned electronically to identify and filter out likely spam and for viruses or related problems that could harm your equipment, the network or other users.

### Law Enforcement

Legal Requirements –We regularly receive legal requests for customer information from government and law enforcement personnel. We also receive discovery requests in civil litigation. In all such cases, our policy is to cooperate as required by law, but to provide only such information, as the law requires. This information is generally sought by subpoena served on us. Under current law, many criminal subpoenas require that we not disclose or notify you of the request. Due to this fact and the volume of requests we receive, we cannot assume any duty to notify you of receipt of any legal requests.

The law does permit us to disclose to law enforcement, voluntarily and without prior notice, customer information, including the contents of communications, if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury requires such disclosure without delay.

### Internet Security

Taking Proper Precautions – Maintaining the security of your own personal computer is an important part of protecting your own privacy and of helping us protect our network and our customer’s service. You should use and update regularly your antivirus software, firewall and your operating system to prevent unauthorized access by others and harm from various forms of viruses. Persons with questionable intent may use the Internet or email to pose as someone you trust or do business with. You should always be sure whom you are dealing with before responding with personal information. To avoid all these and other forms of attacks, we encourage you to visit the Federal Trade Commission (“FTC”) for updates and tips on protecting yourself.

Personal Information – We use “Secure Socket Layer” encryption technology when collecting certain personal information through our websites. You can identify the use of such protection by looking for “https” in the Internet url or page address or a closed lock symbol if you are using Internet Explorer. We protect personally identifiable information found in our most sensitive databases in encrypted formats within controlled and secure environments with restricted access. While we attempt to ensure the integrity and security of our network and computer systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent unauthorized access.

### Children’s Privacy

Our websites are not directed at, or intended for use by, children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly allow anyone under 18 to provide any personal information on our websites. You can find more information about protecting children’s privacy by contacting the FTC or viewing its website at http://www.ftc.gov.

### Changes in Policy

Developments in the Internet, the law, our offerings and websites may cause us to change this Online Privacy Policy from time to time. Any such changes will be prospective and will not affect information collected prior to the change in policy.

### California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights

California law permits residents who have provided personal information to us to request information about disclosure of personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes. As detailed above, our policy is not to disclose personal information collected online or otherwise for any third party’s direct marketing purposes without first obtaining the customer’s consent.
